<rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" version="2.0"><channel><title>Ron Becker</title><description>Because I'm Important!</description><link>http://localhost:2368/</link><image><url>http://localhost:2368/favicon.png</url><title>Ron Becker</title><link>http://localhost:2368/</link></image><generator>Ghost 3.1</generator><lastBuildDate>Sat, 30 Nov 2019 13:05:45 GMT</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://localhost:2368/rss/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><ttl>60</ttl><item><title>Use Ghost for GitHub Pages</title><description>&lt;p&gt;There are a lot of great options for creating static sites to use with &lt;a href="https://pages.github.com/"&gt;GitHub Pages&lt;/a&gt;. The "go to" seems to be Jekyll. But, some of use like other options much better. Like &lt;a href="https://ghost.org"&gt;Ghost&lt;/a&gt;! The only problem is Ghost isn't a static site generator like Jekyll. Typically you need to&lt;/p&gt;</description><link>http://localhost:2368/use-ghost-for-github-pages/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5de25d29d38eb20df96f084e</guid><category>GitHub Pages</category><category>GitHub</category><category>Ghost</category><category>Static Site Generator</category><dc:creator>Ron Becker</dc:creator><pubDate>Sat, 30 Nov 2019 13:03:42 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;There are a lot of great options for creating static sites to use with &lt;a href="https://pages.github.com/"&gt;GitHub Pages&lt;/a&gt;. The "go to" seems to be Jekyll. But, some of use like other options much better. Like &lt;a href="https://ghost.org"&gt;Ghost&lt;/a&gt;! The only problem is Ghost isn't a static site generator like Jekyll. Typically you need to install Ghost on your server to use it. But, there is a way around that!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This site is actually a Ghost site. So, that is what I'm going to go over today.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h4 id="requirements"&gt;Requirements&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Linux - you can adjust this guide to fit what distro you like best, but I'm going to be making it using Ubuntu.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;An active internet connection.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;The ability to understand me. This is by far the most difficult requirement to meet. Because, I'm not very good with words.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h3 id="setup-and-install-the-prerequisits"&gt;Setup and Install the Prerequisits&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;There are a few things we will need to set up first. The first thing we are going to cover is getting our workspace setup. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;h4 id="install-node-js"&gt;Install Node.js&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ghost is written in Node.js so we will need to install the Node.js runtime. As of right now Ghost doesn't support Node.js v13, so we will need to install v12. Luckily it's a super simple process.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Just enter the following commands into your terminal:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;code&gt;curl -sL https://deb.nodesource.com/setup_12.x | sudo -E bash -&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;code&gt;sudo apt-get install -y nodejs&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Node.js and npm should now be installed, and ready to go!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h4 id="install-ghost-locally"&gt;Install Ghost Locally&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;p&gt;Now that we have Node.js and npm we can install Ghost locally. The first thing we want to do is install the Ghost CLI tool.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;code&gt;npm install ghost-cli -g&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Then we will make a Ghost directory, cd into it, and install Ghost by running the following commands:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;code&gt;mkdir ghost&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;code&gt;cd ghost&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;code&gt;ghost install local&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This should install ghost, and start it for you automatically. If it doesn't you can run this command:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;code&gt;ghost start&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Use your browser to navigate to &lt;code&gt;http://localhost:2368/ghost&lt;/code&gt; to create your account, and access the admin panel. From here you can start reading the get started posts, adjust your settings, and start writting your own blog posts.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h4 id="prepare-your-static-folder"&gt;Prepare Your Static Folder&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;p&gt;For this I'm going to assume you've already created your &lt;code&gt;username.github.io&lt;/code&gt; repo. I created my static folder inside of my ghost folder. It just felt a lot easier for me. What we are going to do is clone our &lt;code&gt;username.github.io&lt;/code&gt; repo to a folder named static. By running a command like this: &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;code&gt;git clone &lt;a&gt;git@github.com&lt;/a&gt;:username/username.github.io.git static&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h4 id="generate-your-static-site-using-buster-and-deploy-it-to-github-pages"&gt;Generate Your Static Site Using Buster and Deploy it to GitHub Pages&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;p&gt;Now you have Node.js, npm, and Ghost installed. You have a static folder, and a blog post or two ready. The next step is to generate your static site.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It's as simple as&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;code&gt;buster generate --domain=http://localhost:2368&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This will generate a static site into your static folder. There are a couple ways to deploy your site. The first one is:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;code&gt;buster deploy&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;However, I had a few issues with this. So, I decided to add, commit, and push the files in my static folder to GitHub myself.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h4 id="writing-new-blog-posts"&gt;Writing New Blog Posts&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you want to change something, or publish new posts, it's pretty simple. Make sure Ghost is running, and if it isn't run &lt;code&gt;ghost start&lt;/code&gt;, make your changes, generate your static site, and then deploy it like before.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Make just you &lt;code&gt;cd&lt;/code&gt; into your ghost folder before you generate your static site.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That's it. Now you have a working Ghost static site to use for GitHub Pages!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h5 id="bonus-ghostbuster"&gt;Bonus: GhostBuster&lt;/h5&gt;&lt;p&gt;I got tired of typing the buster generate command, since deploy was giving me issues. And, I may have been a little bored. So I made a little script to make it easier. Here is the code:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class="language-bash"&gt;#!/bin/bash
#
# Just a super simple bash script that uses buster
# on my local Ghost install to generate a static
# site for GitLab or GitHub
#
# Of Course it has to look like a badass hacker made it
# So it has to have ASCII at the start
#

echo " "
echo "   _____ _               _   ____            _              "
echo "  / ____| |             | | |  _ \          | |             "
echo " | |  __| |__   ___  ___| |_| |_) |_   _ ___| |_ ___ _ __   "
echo " | | |_ | '_ \ / _ \/ __| __|  _ &amp;lt;| | | / __| __/ _ \ '__|  "
echo " | |__| | | | | (_) \__ \ |_| |_) | |_| \__ \ ||  __/ |     "
echo "  \_____|_| |_|\___/|___/\__|____/ \__,_|___/\__\___|_|     "
echo " "
echo " "
echo "GhostBuster is getting ready to run. It will generate a static version"
echo "of your local Ghost install. Then you can deploy it to GitHub Pages."

# Pause it for 5 seconds so it can be read.
sleep 7s

# Run the buster command to generate and deploy static
# site to GitHub Pages.
buster generate --domain=http://localhost:2368

# Everything needs a completion message!!
echo "GhostBuster has finished generating your static site!"&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;p&gt;Honestly, the important part is at the very bottom... but, still don't you want it to look all hacker and have ASCII? And, I used &lt;code&gt;echo&lt;/code&gt; instead of &lt;code&gt;printf&lt;/code&gt; because I wanted that GhostBuster ASCII to look right. With this script I can just type &lt;code&gt;ghostbuster&lt;/code&gt; and generate the static site.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This isn't really needed or important. I just really enjoy running it.&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title>Hello, World!</title><description>Well, I should at least get an introduction post in here. Right?
My name is Ron, and I like to do a terrible job at web development, and making Frankenstein code projects.</description><link>http://localhost:2368/hello-world/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5de16f64c7f3ad600ce02d6b</guid><category>Updates</category><dc:creator>Ron Becker</dc:creator><pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2019 19:32:06 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;Well, I should at least get an introduction post in here. Right?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;My name is Ron, and I like to do a terrible job at web development, and making Frankenstein code projects. I did live, and house my terrible monsters over at GitHub. But, they changed their password policy while I was gone, and now I'm locked out of my account. Which is whatever. My only issue there is I have spent a week talking to a support person, and they know its me, and I own the account, but they still won't send me the reset link.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Anyways, I'm just another person. I'm not famous in my field, or super gifted, I don't even have any popular projects I've started, or helped with. What I do have is a computer, accounts on GitHub and GitLab, an unhealthy need to have multiple websites, and an unsupported feeling of importance. I mean I even went through the trouble to set up a &lt;a href="https://ghost.org"&gt;Ghost&lt;/a&gt; blog as a static site for GitLab/GitHub Pages. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Clearly, I am committed to making myself look like a fool, or super important, by writing bad articles, and updates on my projects, or whatever else tickles my fancy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;So, yeah, I'm sorry... buckle up, put on your helmet, and get ready for this mess!&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item></channel></rss>