<rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" version="2.0"><channel><title>Ron Becker</title><description>Because I'm Important!</description><link>http://localhost:2368/</link><image><url>http://localhost:2368/favicon.png</url><title>Ron Becker</title><link>http://localhost:2368/</link></image><generator>Ghost 3.1</generator><lastBuildDate>Sat, 30 Nov 2019 05:16:45 GMT</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://localhost:2368/rss/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><ttl>60</ttl><item><title>Hello, World!</title><description>Well, I should at least get an introduction post in here. Right?
My name is Ron, and I like to do a terrible job at web development, and making Frankenstein code projects.</description><link>http://localhost:2368/hello-world/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5de16f64c7f3ad600ce02d6b</guid><category>Updates</category><dc:creator>Ron Becker</dc:creator><pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2019 19:32:06 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;Well, I should at least get an introduction post in here. Right?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;My name is Ron, and I like to do a terrible job at web development, and making Frankenstein code projects. I did live, and house my terrible monsters over at GitHub. But, they changed their password policy while I was gone, and now I'm locked out of my account. Which is whatever. My only issue there is I have spent a week talking to a support person, and they know its me, and I own the account, but they still won't send me the reset link.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Anyways, I'm just another person. I'm not famous in my field, or super gifted, I don't even have any popular projects I've started, or helped with. What I do have is a computer, accounts on GitHub and GitLab, an unhealthy need to have multiple websites, and an unsupported feeling of importance. I mean I even went through the trouble to set up a &lt;a href="https://ghost.org"&gt;Ghost&lt;/a&gt; blog as a static site for GitLab/GitHub Pages. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Clearly, I am committed to making myself look like a fool, or super important, by writing bad articles, and updates on my projects, or whatever else tickles my fancy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;So, yeah, I'm sorry... buckle up, put on your helmet, and get ready for this mess!&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item></channel></rss>